I didn't notice anything unusual about His Majesty.
Could it be some new trick?
Just a packet of powdered sugar.
Nothing new.
I don't understand.
Just a trick to test one's loyalty.
If Cangyue had given the powdered sugar to His Majesty,
she would be framing the Grand Princess of Donglin.
She would surely die.
Now that she has actually put the poison
into His Majesty's meals,
she has proven herself trustworthy.
How do you plan to use her?
Isn't His Majesty quite interested in this girl?
Go tell her
to keep His Majesty hooked.
Once he brings a woman to the court and disrupts the state affairs,
his important officials will surely turn their backs on him.
Then without you lifting a finger,
he will lose his throne.
Hahaha.
Now we just wait for him to fall into the trap.
Eldest Princess, Eunuch Sun.
Let's see how you eat this side dish.
So beautiful.
Your Majesty.
Let me see how your painting is going.
Want to see it?
Yes.
Hmph, you're terrible.
Your Majesty, where are we going to play later?
Where do you want to play?
I will accompany you there.
Then I want to play in your heart.
What a bad influence.
Absolutely ridiculous.
You've been standing for a while.
Speak.
Your Majesty.
It is time to select a new batch of palace maids.
After all, this concerns the stability of the state.
Your Majesty, the drought is ongoing.
Crops are failing everywhere.
I implore Your Majesty to issue a disaster relief decree immediately.
Do not indulge in beauty.
I disagree.
Your Majesty should take more concubines to fill the harem
to stabilize the court.
Enough.
I think Chancellor Zhou is right.
Aunt.
Having Cangyue is enough for me right now.
As for other matters,
I don't want to get involved.
Xuan, a monarch cannot be without an heir.
Selecting concubines early to consolidate the harem is what matters.
Ridiculous.
Most of the concubines and maids in his harem
are spies planted by the Grand Princess during the draft.
Aunt.
Your Majesty.
Quick, summon the royal physician.
Your Majesty, how can I live without you?
Am I not going to make it?
I will just watch you put on a show.
I haven't even had time to make you my consort.
I don't want to die.
So,
Just speak your mind.
It's this handkerchief.
This handkerchief clearly has Aunt's name on it.
This fabric is also unique in the palace.
Only Aunt uses it.
Aunt.
Why did you want to harm me?
Your Majesty, I am wronged.
Someone must be trying to frame me.
Frame you?
Who would dare frame you?
And who would dare use aunt's personal handkerchief to frame you?
The only one who can get close to His Majesty now
is this bitch.
Maybe she is the one trying to murder His Majesty.
Speak. Why did you do this?
You mean she did it?
Who would poison themselves while poisoning me?
Your Majesty, Her Highness has never been to your bedchamber.
I can testify for her.
Then how do you explain that handkerchief?
Your Majesty, I am truly innocent.
Although these methods are not clever,
letting him continue to cause trouble
won't do me any good.
Your Majesty.
His Highness would never do such a treasonous thing.
It seems this won't end without someone to take the blame.
That upright old man Shen Qingyan is also present.
Forget it.
It's him then.
Besides this woman,
the only person who can get close to the Emperor
is Eunuch Sun.
Your Majesty.
It wasn't me, Your Majesty.
Princess,
how can you slander me like this?
I am wholeheartedly devoted to you.
Sun Liang has followed His Majesty for so many years,
yet he dared to harm His Majesty.
As His Majesty's aunt,
I cannot turn a blind eye to this.
Guards, take him away.
Your Majesty.
Now that this traitor is dead,
please calm your anger.
Otherwise,
it would be bad for your health.
Investigate.
Investigate this thoroughly.
Find everyone connected to Sun Liang.
Even if you have to search the entire palace,
find anyone related to Sun Liang.
Your Majesty? Is there anything else, Aunt?
Your Majesty.
Since the truth has come to light,
I won't delay your grand plans any longer.